Thank you.
Fightin' God!
the top of the tower.
What's happening?
He's heading down to the
crypt to escape from the
other side.
I get it now.
Bucciarati must have fastened
the brooch to the boss.
Giorno, sorry to bother you,
but could you pass me the water?
I'm feeling parched.
But remember, we must tread carefully.
We have very strict orders to remain right
here on the boat and
to stay off the island,
no matter what the reason. Right.
Uh-huh.
Wait, what you just
couldn't help yourself.
Could you give it back before I start?
What's with all that
sticky goop on your face?
Well as if playing stupid
is gonna fool anyone.
Why'd you have a chance
to stuff your face?
There was no time
By the way, did I thank you?
You know for the bottle of water.
It's refreshing what
Something bizarre is going on.
I don't know what's going on
here, but I've got a bad feeling.
Hey, idiot!
What part of our order to not
disembark was confusing to you? Huh?
We are in deep trouble.
The world, it's not working the
way it should. Merida! Bucciarati!
What the hell? Giorno!
Is that you? Bucciarati.
Yeah, it's me.
Don't worry, I'm already tracking him.
The brooch tells me his exact location.
The bastard is ours.
He's currently at the bottom
of the stairway to the crypt.
No, wait!
Now he's by the pillar
two meters off the stairs!
Don't engage him, Bucciarati!
I don't know what, but something's wrong!
Bucciarati, your mission as
protector has been terminated,
and your life shall promptly follow it.
Cunning little, you're trying
to pin down my arm. Superman!
But Emperor Crimson has seen through you!
It's peered through time
to trace your trajectory,
the trajectory of your future self.
When Emperor Crimson wields its extraordinary
power, time as we know it flits away,
and But all memories formed
therein completely cease to exist.
Clouds are torn asunder and know not why.
The flickering flame is blotted away
without any consciousness of its demise.
All that remains are consequences.
The omnipotence of my time obliterating
powers renders all action futile.
Only I have the ability to
respond to these actions.
I can foretell the exact
flavor of your intentions.
Now feel the power of Emperor Crimson!
This ability...
it's...
No being is immune to
the peaks and valleys
of life as the strong struggle to survive.
One succeeds while the other fails.
But with my power, one can gaze upon
life's pitfalls in all their glory.
Sidestepping them becomes but a chore,
and life becomes a succession of triumphs.
A state of personal perfection.
And truly, how could it not?
Having now met you in the flesh,
I know beyond a shadow of a doubt
that we are indeed connected by blood!
I feel it in my very bones!
You child are my daughter!
Unfortunately for you, as long
as you continue to draw breath,
you'll also feel the blood
connection the two of us share!
I shall obliterate any
peril that stands in my way!
I will sever?
our familial bond as we speak to Trish!
What is happening?
It's Chorno.
That power is courtesy of Golden Wind.
He implanted the brooch with cells
from the turtle, giving them new life.
That's how he was able to
replicate the turtle's stand.
Since we were interrupted, he sensed
danger and activated his ability.
That man never ceases to stoke
the courage within my heart.
I was certain this was
the end, but not yet.
I still have a little
bit of fight left in me.
If you think my mission's
done, boss, you're wrong.
Our future awaits us.
As for Trish, she will be
protected under my mandate.
So,
he has the power to
anticipate all of my attacks
and dodge them before
I've even realized it.
Damn it.
The bastard's practically invincible.
However, there is a limit.
He can only read his opponent's
movements in short bursts.
What a transient trick.
He can cheat time for five to ten seconds.
Distance.
I need to create more distance between us.
Enough that the boss can't capture Trish.
Come on, Bruno. Move!
Jono's given you an opportunity.
I just need to get us
out of this basement.
Seems there's another
traitor in our midst.
My guess would be the neophyte.
Assuming my sources are correct,
his name is Giorno Giovanna.
So he had every intention of betraying
me from the very beginning, did he?
Charming that you think
distance will aid your escape.
Stopping you is as easy as
exiting the turtle before you act.
You are utterly pathetic, Uchirati.
Is it inner strength that
allows you to continue to move?
Just rest your weary head.
You'll never reach the first floor,
but you'll be assured a painless end.
And Trish will finally meet her maker!
Now remain still, Uchirati!
I've been given a golden chance!
Do you think I'd waste it?
While you were bragging
about reading my movements,
I took the liberty of reading yours!
I knew you wouldn't just
disappear into the sewers,
not before trying to escape
with your powers! Do it!
Superman!
Emperor Crimson!
That was quite the close call.
But this is the world of Emperor Crimson.
In this domain, your
efforts are forever in vain.
This is your end! Perish!
My target wasn't you in the
first place it was this pillar.
Quickly, zipper, close!
What I was right one might
call your power invincible
but that same ability
also has Its limitations.
You're not seeing into the
future not truly anyway.
I challenge you to to predict
what my next move is going to be.
It's really anyone's guess what
the next few seconds will hold.
I invite you to face the future head-on,
as you're greeted by the sight of me,
while on the ground floor.
Bucinati! Trish!
This wound!
What happened down in the crypt?
The boss!
He's got to be here, somewhere close by.
I don't know what went down,
but one thing's for sure.
The boss won't tolerate
any act of defiance!
It can't be.
No!
Bucciarati!
It's gone.
His pulse is gone.
I made the new park.
He should be breathing.
Bucciarati, breathe!
So this is the Giorno Giovanna.
Interesting.
He intended to use his power to give
Bucciarati another chance at life.
How sad.
It was such a valiant effort.
Impossible.
The replacement should have worked.
Why the hell doesn't he have a pulse?
Giorno, it's me.
Call the Bakio and the others.
You have to escape now.
That voice.
I said to call Abacchio and the others.
Get out of here.
Leave the tower.
Now.
Pucinacci, Crazy Dio.
You're okay. Forget me.
Call the others. But I...
For the time being, the boss's
identity will have to remain a mystery.
We have to escape.
Our lead won't last.
You're within range. Let's begin.
I'll explain everything later.
We need to hurry, Giorno!
Golden win!
Giorno's over there!
Giorno, get your ass back here!
How do you think the boss is gonna react
when he hears you refuse
to stay in the boat?
Bucciaranti's here too!
What the heck happened to you?
You look awful!
And why is Trish knocked out in your arms?
Bucciarati, what's going on?
I'll explain later.
Getting out of this building comes first.
I salute you, Bucciarati.
Truly, you are a man
of unnerring judgment.
I may have the power to
obliterate time at my fingertips,
but facing six stand users would
inevitably review my identity.
Now is not the time.
You are fortunate to
survive Emperor Crimson,
but know your fortuitousness
will be short-lived.
I swear, you shall die here.
Venice will be your watery grave!
I figured out his twisted method.
I now know how he foments
fear and clings to power.
We can't defeat the boss, not just yet.
His identity...
Assuming he has any weaknesses,
we'll need to unveil his flaws
before trying to take him.
What is this, Bucciarati?
We deserve some answers, so
you better start talking!
You're right.
I'll cut to the chase.
I can't go into detail but the
fact is we're in terrible danger.
I've brought Trish back to us to save her
and I've committed to betraying the boss!
Unfortunately my friends this
is where we part ways if you
choose to join me you'd also
be choosing life on the run
what are you saying yeah you're
not making any sense I I don't
think I heard you right yes
you did he said he's betraying
the boss our boss but but why
for your safety let's end the
conversation here all I can
say is this is my choice no I
really think you should
elaborate some of them might want
to join us if they hear you
out and besides we'll need help
you're a piece of work
Giorno you know that first
you stormed the tower like
you You own the place,
and now you...
Mucinati!
Hey, what's the matter?
How can I help you?
Don't worry about me.
I'm fine.
The blood loss made me a
little dizzy, that's all.
It doesn't make sense.
I replaced the wound with healthy
tissue and replenished his blood.
What could I have missed?
I'm just fatigued from this whole ordeal.
Why didn't he feel that?
And for that matter,
why isn't he bleeding?
What's going on?
Excuse me.
You had me worried there.
Yeah, no kidding. Please,
don't go. Don't do this.
Ujarati, at the very least,
we deserve an explanation.
Fine.
The boss only had us
protect his daughter so
that he'd be assured he
could kill her himself.
Due to their connection, she
has insight into his identity.
Once I learned the truth, I...
I knew he couldn't be forgiven.
And I couldn't stand before you
and ignore his vile depravity.
I had to betray him.
I don't believe this.
Have you lost it, Bucciarati?
I didn't think I'd ever
have to remind you of this.
But you know what the
boss does to traitors.
He punishes all who cross
him without exception.
In fact, for all our group knows, his
guards could have this place on lockdown.
Yes, which is why I'm
going to need your help.
If you choose to join in this operation,
then descend the stairs
and get on the boat.
Let me be clear, this is not
an order, but an invitation.
This decision is entirely yours to make.
I understand what I'm getting myself into,
and you're under no
obligation to follow me.
Believe me, I realize how
all this must seem to you.
But the actions I take
are righteous and just.
I've no regrets.
Though our world is unjust, I will
strive to walk the path I believe in.
Our retreat today isn't a defeat.
Once we find his weakness,
I'll bring down the boss.
He will be toppled.
I understand.
I believe you're trying
to do good, Pucurati.
That said, I have to speak my truth, too.
It hurts to say, but no
one is coming with you.
I'm surprised you're being so sentimental.
I owe you my life, but I
can't be a part of this.
You've lost touch with reality.
Lofty ideals alone won't get
you through this difficult life.
We could never survive without the Family.
You should listen to him.
You've basically put the
gun in your own damn mouth.
There's nowhere you can hide now.
You'll have to live
life always on the run.
Remember, I pledged my loyalties
to the Family at large.
And it's not like I ever
swore any allegiance to you.
But even so, I've never had
a place to really call home.
A place where I really felt
like I belonged, you know?
The only time I've felt at ease is...
Well, when I'm with you, Bucciarati.
Abacchio.
What?
You can't! Abacchio!
Well, considering my skills,
if we get rid of the boss, I'll
be next in line to beat Cabo.
Listen, Bucciarati's
as smart as they come.
No way in hell he'd take on
an opponent he couldn't beat.
We're gonna be rolling
in sweet lira, amico mio.
Mister!
Not you two!
So, Fugo, what's it gonna
be? You coming with?
You're crazy!
You've all lost your minds!
We'd be completely isolated!
Where could we possibly run?
We wouldn't even make it
out of the city alive!
Narancia, what are you going to do?
I don't know.
Please, tell me.
What now, Bucciarati? Help me.
What should I do?
Do you think I should go with you guys?
Are you scared? I am.
I'm honestly scared out of my mind.
I need an order. Give me an order.
Please just tell me to get my
ass in gear like you always do.
Give me an order and I
won't be afraid anymore.
I will not.
I can't decide your fate for you.
The choice must be yours.
Though we walk this world
together, your path belongs to you.
But what does all that even mean?
Dammit, what am I supposed to do?
Listen, a word of caution.
Stay here, Narancia.
This is not your fight.
Then you're serious you'll
end up six feet under?
I get what you're doing
but there's some things In
this world you just can't
change being mafiosi means
we can't always take the
high ground How's this
mission different from any
of the other dirty ones?
I can't answer that I just know I
refuse To live a lie let's be off our
departure will mark the beginning of
our lives as traitors to the Mafia.
Come on guys, think about
what you're doing here.
We just met this girl, why throw your lives
away for someone you know nothing about?
She won't even tell us what
kind of music she likes.
She was betrayed by the one she
thought she could trust the most.
I know how she feels, I know that pain.
My own father, the people I thought
were my friends, they abandoned me.
We're the same.
We've both been through hell.
The world's kicked both of us
around, and so I have to...
Jonah, the turtle, please.
Trish can hide inside. Got it.
You should really take a
look behind you. Bucciarati!
I'm going with you! I'm right here!
Don't leave me!
Please don't tell me to stay behind!
Trish and I are the same!
Her wounds are my wounds! Her pain!
It's my pain!
Narancia, you're turning two.
You fool, you're going to be killed.
I just can't be a part of this
ridiculous game of betrayal.
I won't be a martyr. I refuse.
You sure took your sweet-ass
time getting here, buddy.
You better not bitch
and moan the whole time.
You got it?
Narancia, you'll forever have
my respect for doing this.
So, Fugo stayed behind after all.
Well, that was his decision to make.
Bucciarati, I want to protect
Trish with everything I've got.
I swear to defeat the boss with you.
Sounds good.
Squalo?
Looks like we've got ourselves
some traitors in Venice.
Their names?
Bruno Bucciarati and Giorno Giovanna.
Capture them dead or alive.
These are the boss's direct orders.
Thank you.